John W. Tukey Papers 1937-2000 Mss.Ms.Coll.117
American Philosophical Society
- Series I. Correspondence, 1938-2000; 60 linear feet
  - Nemenyi, Peter, 1953-1969; 8 items (Box 24)
  - Ness, Ordean Gerhard, 1978-1979; 3 item (Box 24)
  - Neter, John, 1966-1969; 4 items (Box 24)
  - Netschert, William, 1948-1968; 13 items (Box 24)
  - Neuwirth, Sidney I., 1953-1954; 13 items (Box 24)
  - New England journal of medicine, 1987-1988; 7 items (Box 24)
  - New York Academy of Medicine, 1977-1982; 6 items (Box 24)
  - New York Academy of Sciences, 1948-1949; Folder 1 (Box 24)
  - New York Academy of Sciences, 1950-1964; Folder 2 (Box 24)
  - New York Entomologist, 1948; 14 items (Box 24)
  - New York University, 1953-1978; 15 items (Box 24)
  - Newark Air Procurement District, 1953-1956; 10 items (Box 24)
  - Newman, David F., 1954; 2 items (Box 24)
  - Newman, Lorne T., 1960; 2 items (Box 24)
  - Newman, Marian, 1997; 2 items (Box 24)
  - Neyman, Jerzy, 1894-?, 1958-1980; Folder 1 (Box 24)
  - Neyman, Jerzy, 1894-?, n.d.; Folder 2 (Box 24)
  - Nguyen, Ha, 1984-1993; 26 items (Box 24)
  - Niblett, G. B. F., 1968-1969; 3 items (Box 24)
  - Nicholson, George, 1955-1967; 24 items (Box 24)
  - Nicholson, Wesley Lathrop, 1929-?, 1973-1987; 21 items (Box 24)
  - Niedzielski, E. L., 1954; 1 item (Box 24)
  - Niessen, A. M., 1962; 3 items (Box 24)
  - Nilsson, Carl-Axel, 1993; 4 items (Box 24)
  - Nixon, Richard M. (Richard Milhous), 1913-1994, 1970; 1 item (Box 24)
  - Nobles, Melvin Alfred, 1954; 3 items (Box 24)
  - Noe, Norman, 1981; 5 items (Box 24)
  - Noel, Thomas, 1966; 1 item (Box 24)
  - Noether, Gottfried E. (Gottfried Emanuel), 1955-1963; 13 items (Box 24)
  - Nolting, Alfred R., 1974; 7 items (Box 24)
  - Northam, Jack I., 1956; 1 item (Box 24)
  - Northrop Aircraft, 1951; 3 items (Box 24)
  - Northrop, Doyle, 1960; 1 item (Box 24)
  - Norton, H. W., 1951-1960; 4 items (Box 24)
  - Nosanchuk, T. A., 1935-?, 1969-1981; 15 items (Box 24)
  - Novick, Melvin, 1975-1978; 11 items (Box 24)
  - Noyes, W. Albert (William Albert), 1898-1980, 1946; 2 items (Box 24)
  - Nye, John F., 1964; 2 items (Box 24)
  - O'Brian, Francis L., 1983-1984; 17 items (Box 24)
  - O'Callaghan, John, n.d.; 3 items (Box 24)
  - Oakley, Cletus O. (Cletus Odia), 1899-?, 1941-1978; 20 items (Box 24)
  - Oakley, Howard T., 1955; 2 items (Box 24)
  - Odbert, Henry S., 1972; 2 items (Box 25)
  - Office of Naval Research, 1947-1949; 7 items (Box 25)
  - Office of Naval Research, 1946-1951; Folder 1 (Box 25)
  - Office of Naval Research, 1952; Folder 2 (Box 25)
  - Office of Naval Research, 1953-1956; Folder 3 (Box 25)
  - Office of Naval Research - Rees, Mina, 1946-1949; 17 items (Box 25)
  - Office of Naval Research - Rigby, Fred, 1947-1949; 7 items (Box 25)
  - Office of Ordnance Research, U.S. Army, 1955; 10 items (Box 25)
  - Office of the Director of Defense Research and Engineering, 1965; 1 item (Box 25)
  - Office of the Secretary of Defense, 1956; 2 items (Box 25)
  - Ogg, Clyde L., 1950; 1 item (Box 25)
  - Ohman, Carl R., 1951-1955; 12 items (Box 25)
  - Oldford, Wayne, 1986; 3 items (Box 25)
  - Olds, Edward B., 1954; 1 item (Box 25)
  - Oliver, Bernard M., 1916-?, 1960-1980; 5 items (Box 25)
  - Olkin, Ingram, 1952-1961; 7 items (Box 25)
  - Olson, Norman A., 1952-1955; 10 items (Box 25)
  - Operation Ballet, 1960-1961; 3 items (Box 25)
  - Operations Research Office, 1953-1955; 3 items (Box 25)
  - Operations Research Society of America, 1953-1959; 11 items (Box 25)
  - Oppenheimer, Jack, 1969; 2 items (Box 25)
  - Oregon State College, 1953-1956; 4 items (Box 25)
  - Orientation Tests, 1966; 1 item (Box 25)
  - Oser, Jacob, 1915-?, 1952; 3 items (Box 25)
  - Osgood, Charles Egerton, 1916-?, 1967; 2 items (Box 25)
  - Oster, Gerald, 1949-1983; 5 items (Box 25)
  - Overhage, Carl F. J., 1910-?, 1965; 2 items (Box 25)
  - Owen, A. R. G. (Alan Robert George), 1919-?, 1955; 10 items (Box 25)
  - Owen, D. B. (Donald Bruce), 1922-?, 1961-1983; 20 items (Box 25)
  - Pabst, William Richard, 1911-?, 1951-1956; 16 items (Box 25)
  - Packer, Margaret, n.d.; 3 items (Box 25)
  - Padmanabhan, A. R., 1984-1986; 6 items (Box 25)
  - Page, Chester Hall, 1938-1950; 3 items (Box 25)
  - Panel on Arms Limitation and Control, 1960; 2 items (Box 25)
  - Panofsky, Hans A., 1951-1981; 26 items (Box 25)
  - Panofsky, Wolfgang Kurt Hermann, 1919-?, 1960; 2 items (Box 25)
  - Parker, George H., 1959; 1 item (Box 25)
  - Parks, T. W., 1980-1981; 9 items (Box 25)
  - Parrish, Gene B., 1963-1964; 2 items (Box 25)
  - Parunak, Anita, 1973-1982; Folder 1 (Box 25)
  - Parunak, Anita, 1984-1986; Folder 2 (Box 25)
  - Parunak, Anita, 1987-1989; Folder 3 (Box 25)
  - Parzen, Emanuel, 1929-, 1955-1970; Folder 1 (Box 25)
  - Parzen, Emanuel, 1929-, 1978-1989; Folder 2 (Box 25)
  - Patankar, V. N., 1955; 5 items (Box 25)
  - Patents, 1956-1964; 4 items (Box 25)
  - Patil, G. P., 1973-1987; 18 items (Box 25)
  - Patte, W. E., 1946-1947; 7 items (Box 25)
  - Patterson, Blossom H., 1990; 8 items (Box 25)
  - Patterson, C. H., 1955; 2 items (Box 25)
  - Patterson, Gardiner, 1961; 1 item (Box 25)
  - Paull, Daniel, 1972; 3 items (Box 25)
  - Paull, Richard, 1963-1965; 5 items (Box 25)
  - Paulsen, Susan, 1984; 4 items (Box 25)
  - Paulson, Albert S., 1981-1988; 8 items (Box 25)
  - Paxson, Edward W., 1938-1947; 6 items (Box 25)
  - Payne, Howard, 1955; 3 items (Box 25)
  - Payne, Maxwell, 1954; 3 items (Box 25)
  - Payne, Michael, 1992; 2 items (Box 25)
  - Peach, Paul, 1950-1951; 4 items (Box 25)
  - Peaker, G. F., 1969; 11 items (Box 25)
  - Pearce, S. C., 1952-1976; 11 items (Box 25)
  - Pearson, E. S. (Egon Sharpe), 1895-, 1955-1961; Folder 1 (Box 25)
  - Pearson, E. S. (Egon Sharpe), 1895-, 1962-1966; Folder 2 (Box 25)
  - Peck, Stephen, 1992; 2 items (Box 25)
  - Pedersen, Jan, 1988-1991; 16 items (Box 25)
  - Peisakoff, Melvin, 1949-1954; 23 items (Box 25)
  - Pennsylvania State University, 1974; 7 items (Box 25)
  - Penzias, Arno A., 1982-1983; 4 items (Box 25)
  - Peoples, J. A., 1961; 3 items (Box 25)
  - Perdie, Patricia R., 1957-1958; 4 items (Box 25)
  - Perkins, Harvey, 1951; 2 items (Box 25)
  - Perlis, Alan J., 1969; 4 items (Box 25)
  - Perlman, Michael D., 1968-1985; 12 items (Box 25)
  - Permuted Index to Minimum Abbreviation, 1 item (Box 25)
  - Peterson, R. P., 1950; 3 items (Box 25)
  - Peterson, Walter, 1952-1957; 2 items (Box 25)
  - Petition, 1939; 17 items (Box 25)
  - Petterson, Sverre, 1962; 2 items (Box 25)
  - Pettis, Billy J., 1939; 1 item (Box 25)
  - Pew, Richard W., 1957; 2 items (Box 25)
  - Pfann, W. G., 1960; 2 items (Box 25)
  - Phalen, Robert, 1993; 3 items (Box 25)
  - Phillips, Almarin, 1953-1960; 4 items (Box 25)
  - Phillips. R. S., 1941; 3 items (Box 25)
  - Phinney, R. A., 1965; 1 item (Box 25)
  - Picatinny Arsenal, 1954-1955; 4 items (Box 25)
  - Pickle, Linda, 1998; 6 items (Box 25)
  - Pielou, E. C., 1974; 2 items (Box 25)
  - Pierce, Donald A., 1965; 5 items (Box 25)
  - Pierce, John R., 1956-1963; Folder 1 (Box 25)
  - Pierce, John R., 1967-1979; Folder 2 (Box 25)
  - Pierson, Willard J., 1951-1965; 15 items (Box 25)
  - Pieters, Richard, 1975; 3 items (Box 26)
  - Pike, Eugene W., 1948-1969; 39 items (Box 26)
  - Pillai, K. C. S., 1951-1967; 19 items (Box 26)
  - Pincus, Howard J., 1953-1954; 3 items (Box 26)
  - Pinkham, Roger S., 1955-1984; 21 items (Box 26)
  - Pinter, Louis, 1962-1963; 3 items (Box 26)
  - Piore, Emanuel R., 1970-1985; 6 items (Box 26)
  - Piovia, Frank, 1965; 2 items (Box 26)
  - Pisarenko, V. F., 1971; 2 items (Box 26)
  - Pitman, E. J. G., 1955-1956; 4 items (Box 26)
  - Pittendrigh, Colin, 1956-1958; 4 items (Box 26)
  - Pittet, Pierre F., 1995; 5 items (Box 26)
  - Plagemann, S. H., 1968; 2 items (Box 26)
  - Polissar, Lincoln T., 1966-1974; 25 items (Box 26)
  - Pollak, Barth, 1952; 2 items (Box 26)
  - Pollak, Henry O., 1958-1972; 17 items (Box 26)
  - Pollard, H. S., 1955; 1 item (Box 26)
  - Pollin, Jack, 1978; 2 items (Box 26)
  - Pollock, Donald K., 1968; 1 item (Box 26)
  - Pondy, P. R., 1954; 1 item (Box 26)
  - Porter, Douglas, 1987; 1 item (Box 26)
  - Posener, Ludwig, 1964; 3 items (Box 26)
  - Potter, H. D., 1965; 5 items (Box 26)
  - Potter, Paul Edwin, 1957; 10 items (Box 26)
  - Potter, Thomas, 1985; 7 items (Box 26)
  - Pounds, William F., 1972-1977; 2 items (Box 26)
  - Pournelle, Jerry, 1986; 4 items (Box 26)
  - Prager, Stephen, 1977; 4 items (Box 26)
  - Prager, William, 1942-1961; 23 items (Box 26)
  - Pratt, John W., 1952-1988; 40 items (Box 26)
  - Preece, Donald, 1982; 2 items (Box 26)
  - Pregibon, Daryl, 1978-1990; 21 (Box 26)
  - President's Reorganization Project, 1977-1978; 4 items (Box 26)
  - President's Science Advisory Committee, 1965-1974; 8 items (Box 26)
  - Presidents Commission on Federal Statistics, 1970-1976; 17 items (Box 26)
  - Presidents Committee on the National Medal of Science, 1990; 1 item (Box 26)
  - Press, Frank, 1960-1992; 10 items (Box 26)
  - Press, Harry, 1952-1960; 20 items (Box 26)
  - Press, William, 1992; 3 items (Box 26)
  - Preston, Glenn W., 1955-1981; 6 items (Box 26)
  - Prevas, James, 1955-1956; 2 items (Box 26)
  - Prevost, Jean H., 1989-1991; 5 items (Box 26)
  - Price, Derek J., 1963-1966; 10 items (Box 26)
  - Price, G. Baley, (Griffith Baley), 1905-, 1938-1966; 41 items (Box 26)
  - Price, George, 1950-1953; 3 items (Box 26)
  - Priestley, Maurice B., 1961-1980; 19 items (Box 26)
  - Prim, Robert C., 1959-1976; 14 items (Box 26)
  - Prim-9, 1974-1993; 12 items (Box 26)
  - Princeton University, 1941-1961; Folder 1 (Box 26)
  - Princeton University, 1971-1976; Folder 2 (Box 26)
  - Princeton University, 1977-1980; Folder 3 (Box 26)
  - Princeton University, n.d.; Folder 4 (Box 26)
  - Princeton University - Chronicle, 1939; 29 items (Box 26)
  - Princeton University - Mathematics Department, 1945-1953 (Box 26)
  - Princeton University - Matta Poisett, 1947; 21 items (Box 26)
  - Princeton University - Program, 1948; 50 items (Box 26)
  - Princeton University - Schedule, 1946-1953; 51 items (Box 26)
  - Problem of Berkson, A, 1949; 7 items (Box 26)
  - Probst, D. A., 1955; 3 items (Box 26)
  - Project Rand, 1949; 7 items (Box 26)
  - Projector, Murray, 1947; 4 items (Box 26)
  - Pronko, Eugene, 1962-1964; 20 items (Box 26)
  - Proschan, Frank, 1954; 3 items (Box 26)
  - Psychological Test Theory, 1964; 4 items (Box 26)
  - Psychological Bulletin, 1991; 4 items (Box 26)
  - Public Utilities Forecasting Conference, 1977; 6 items (Box 26)
  - Purdue Resaerch Foundation, 1956; 3 items (Box 26)
  - Purdue University, 1956-1982; 8 items (Box 26)
  - Pusey, Nathan M., 1957; 2 items (Box 26)
  - Pyke, Ronald, 1956-1962; 9 items (Box 26)
  - Pypker, B. B., 1962; 2 items (Box 26)
  - Quan, Tony, 1975; 23 items (Box 26)
  - Quandt, R. E., 1965-1974; 3 items (Box 26)
  - Quenouille, M.H., 1951-1958; 3 items (Box 26)
  - Quinn, Alonzo, 1941; 5 items (Box 26)
  - Rack, Leonard, 1951; 4 items (Box 26)
  - Rackley, Karen, 1973; 2 items (Box 26)
  - Radio Corporation of America, 1953-1956; 8 items (Box 26)
  - Radvanyi, Laszlo, 1947-1949; 6 items (Box 26)
  - Rafferty, James A., 1947-1961; 5 items (Box 26)
  - Raftery, Adrian E., 1985; 2 items (Box 26)
  - Rajagopal, V., 1959; 2 items (Box 26)
  - Ramachanchan, K. V., 1956; 2 items (Box 26)
  - Ramo, Simon, 1956-1963; 2 items (Box 26)
  - Ramo-Wooldridge Company, 1956; 3 items (Box 26)
  - Ramsden, Richard, 1976; 2 items (Box 26)
  - Ramsey, James B., 1966-1976; 7 items (Box 26)
  - Ramsey, Philip H., 1982; 2 items (Box 26)
  - Rand Corporation, 1954-1968; 20 items (Box 27)
  - Randolph, Lila, 1964; 3 items (Box 27)
  - Ranganathan, S. R., 1965; 1 item (Box 27)
  - Ransom, Whitney, 1950; 1 item (Box 27)
  - Rao, C. Radhakrishna (Calyampudi Radhakrishna), 1920-, 1954-1971; Folder 1 (Box 27)
  - Rao, C. Radhakrishna (Calyampudi Radhakrishna), 1920-, 1991-1992; Folder 2 (Box 27)
  - Rao, C. Radhakrishna (Calyampudi Radhakrishna), 1920-, 1992-1993; Folder 3 (Box 27)
  - Rao, Gundu, 1959-1960; 3 items (Box 27)
  - Rao, Poduri, 1981-1982; 8 items (Box 27)
  - Rasch, George, 1947-1965; 8 items (Box 27)
  - Rathmacher, Robert, 1987; 2 items (Box 27)
  - Rattner, Zackary, 1980; 4 items (Box 27)
  - Ray, Donald, 1958-1960; 7 items (Box 27)
  - Ray, W. Derek, 1960-1961; 10 items (Box 27)
  - Raymond, A. E., 1947; 1 item (Box 27)
  - Raynault, Paul, 1963-1965; 12 items (Box 27)
  - Rea, W. T., 1956-1962; 2 items (Box 27)
  - Reed, Eliot, 1965; 2 items (Box 27)
  - Reed, Lowell J., 1951; 3 items (Box 27)
  - Rees, Mina, 1946-1967; 6 items (Box 27)
  - Reeve, E. C. R., 1956; 1 item (Box 27)
  - Reiersol, Olav, 1955; 2 items (Box 27)
  - Reiner, Berta, 1988; 2 items (Box 27)
  - Reis, Alfred J., 1948; 2 items (Box 27)
  - Renner, Maynard, 1954; 4 items (Box 27)
  - Resnikoff, George J., 1974; 1 item (Box 27)
  - Resnikoff, Howard, 1972-1987; 23 items (Box 27)
  - Response Analysis, 1975; 2 items (Box 27)
  - Reuter, G. E. H., 1983; 2 items (Box 27)
  - Rheem Manufacturing Company, 1955-1956; 3 items (Box 27)
  - Ricciuti, C., 1953-1954; 5 items (Box 27)
  - Rice University, 1978-1979; 10 items (Box 27)
  - Rice, Stephen, 1953-1975; 5 items (Box 27)
  - Richards, W. A., 1987-1988; 4 items (Box 27)
  - Richardson, B. A., 1968; 2 items (Box 27)
  - Richmond, Donald E., 1955; 3 items (Box 27)
  - Richmond, John, 1981; 8 items (Box 27)
  - Richmond, Martha, 1989-1992; 4 items (Box 27)
  - Richmond, Phyllis, 1965-1966; 11 items (Box 27)
  - Rickhow, Kenneth H., 1978; 2 items (Box 27)
  - Rider, Paul, 1950-1954; 8 items (Box 27)
  - Ridgway, Stuart, 1985; 2 items (Box 27)
  - Riehl, Herbert, 1962; 2 items (Box 27)
  - Rigney, James A., 1948-1952; 8 items (Box 27)
  - Rigsby, Leo C., 1985; 2 items (Box 27)
  - Riley, Donald A., 1955-1984; 6 items (Box 27)
  - Riley, Janet, 1976; 3 items (Box 27)
  - Rimland, Bernard, 1965-1974; 16 items (Box 27)
  - Rinehart, Robert F., 1962; 3 items (Box 27)
  - Riordan, John, 1950-1954; 3 items (Box 27)
  - Rivett, B. H. P., 1954; 4 items (Box 27)
  - Roach, William L., 1954-1980; 10 items (Box 27)
  - Roadel Foods, inc., 1968; 4 items (Box 27)
  - Robbins, Herbert E., 1952-1954; 5 items (Box 27)
  - Roberts, Elizabeth, 1980; 3 items (Box 27)
  - Roberts, Richard B., 1960; 2 items (Box 27)
  - Roberts, Seth, 1980-1994; 10 items (Box 27)
  - Roberts, W. J., 1965; 3 items (Box 27)
  - Robertson, Alan, 1947; 4 items (Box 27)
  - Robinson, David, 1962-1963; 2 items (Box 27)
  - Robinson, Enders, 1953-1978; 7 items (Box 27)
  - Robinson, H. F., 1950; 3 items (Box 27)
  - Robinson, Julia, 1976; 4 items (Box 27)
  - Robson, Douglas S., 1960-1966; 15 items (Box 27)
  - Robust Estimation, 1967-1968; 3 items (Box 27)
  - Robustness Circulation, 1980; 2 items (Box 27)
  - Robustness, 1972-1976; 12 items (Box 27)
  - Roby, Thornton, 1950; 2 items (Box 27)
  - Rocklin, Al, 1938; 1 item (Box 27)
  - Rodgers, John, 1957; 1 item (Box 27)
  - Roeloffs, Robert, 1957-1958; 2 items (Box 27)
  - Rogers, William, 1974; 3 items (Box 27)
  - Rojansky, V., 1942-1962; 5 items (Box 27)
  - Rolph, John, 1985-1990; 2 items (Box 27)
  - Romig, Harry Gutelius, 1900-?, 1947-1948; 5 items (Box 27)
  - Romney, Carl, 1960; 2 items (Box 27)
  - Ronchetti, Elvezio, 1979; Folder 1 (Box 27)
  - Ronchetti, Elvezio, 1982-1988; Folder 2 (Box 27)
  - Rosen, Milton W., 1978; 2 items (Box 27)
  - Rosen, J. B. (Judah Ben), 1922-?, 1962; 2 items (Box 27)
  - Rosenberg, Adam, n.d.; 3 items (Box 27)
  - Rosenberg, Seymour, 1962-1965; 3 items (Box 27)
  - Rosenblatt, Murray, 1961-1987; 21 items (Box 27)
  - Rosenblith, Walter A., 1957-1992; 10 items (Box 27)
  - Rosenblum, F., n.d.; 1 item (Box 27)
  - Rosenthal, Robert, 1933-, 1997-1998; 3 items (Box 27)
  - Ross, I. M., 1981; 2 items (Box 27)
  - Ross, Ian Campbell, 1920-?, 1958-1985; 38 items (Box 27)
  - Rossby, Carl G., 1951-1952; 4 items (Box 27)
  - Rosser, J. Barkley (John Barkley), 1907-?, 1949-1982; 42 items (Box 27)
  - Rossi, Peter Henry, 1921-?, 1964-1971; 3 items (Box 27)
  - Rothamsted Experimental Station, n.d.; 7 items (Box 27)
  - Rottig, Ernst, 1967-1968; 7 items (Box 27)
  - Round Robin, 1946; 13 items (Box 27)
  - Rousseeuw, Peter J., 1985-1988; Folder 1 (Box 27)
  - Rousseeuw, Peter J., 1993-1999; Folder 2 (Box 27)
  - Royal Magic and Novelty Company, 1955; 1 item (Box 27)
  - Royal Statistical Society (Great Britain), 1950-1994; 38 items (Box 27)
  - Rubin, Donald B., 1975-1991; 12 items (Box 27)
  - Ruckelshaus, William Doyle, 1932-?, 1971; 1 box (Box 27)
  - Rudenstine, Neil L, 1974; 1 item (Box 27)
  - Rudnik, Philip, 1951-1953; 2 items (Box 27)
  - Ruina, Jack T., 1963; 1 item (Box 27)
  - Rulon, Phillip Justin, 1900-?, 1950-1952; 4 items (Box 27)
  - Runcorn, S. K., 1954; 4 items (Box 27)
  - Rusnak, Gene A., 1956; 3 items (Box 28)
  - Russell, Carl T., 1987; 9 items (Box 28)
  - Russell, Milton, 1933-?, 1992-1996; 3 items (Box 28)
  - Russell, Sargent, 1954; 2 items (Box 28)
  - Rustagi, Jagdish S., 1981; 3 items (Box 28)
  - Rutherford, J. R., 1974; 5 items (Box 28)
  - Ryan, Louise M. and Paul Catalano, 1990-1993; 9 items (Box 28)
  - Ryan, T. A., 1956-1960; 13 items (Box 28)
  - Safety Committee, 1954; 1 item (Box 28)
  - Sager, Naomi, 1960; 1 item (Box 28)
  - Saint Paul Companies, 1956; 3 items (Box 28)
  - Salomon, Richard, 1975; 7 items (Box 28)
  - Salsburg, David, 1931-?, 1966-1988; 8 items (Box 28)
  - Salton, Gerard, 1962-1970; 8 items (Box 28)
  - Samet, Jonathan M., 1990-1996; 6 items (Box 28)
  - Sampson, Allan R., 1991; 2 items (Box 28)
  - Samuel, Pierre, 1921-?, 1948; 1 item (Box 28)
  - Sandelius, Martin D., 1955-1968; 7 items (Box 28)
  - Sanders, M. T., 1950; 3 items (Box 28)
  - Sandia Corporation, 1953-1955; 13 items (Box 28)
  - Sandiford, Peter J., 1959; 3 items (Box 28)
  - Sandomire, Marion M., 1952-1956; 12 items (Box 28)
  - Sankhya, 1973-1974; 4 items (Box 28)
  - SATCOM, 1966; 1 item (Box 28)
  - Satterthwaite, F. E., 1951-1978; 35 items (Box 28)
  - Saunders, Samuel C., 1964; 1 item (Box 28)
  - Savage, I. Richard, 1951-1988; 45 items (Box 28)
  - Savage, Leonard J., 1952-1971; 29 items (Box 28)
  - Sawyer, Ralph A., 1961; 2 items (Box 28)
  - Sayre, Daniel G., 1955; 2 items (Box 28)
  - Scaff, J. H., 1954; 2 items (Box 28)
  - Scammon, Richard M., 1963; 5 items (Box 28)
  - Schacht, K. G., 1958-1960; 3 items (Box 28)
  - Scheffe, Henry, 1907-1977, 1947-1977; 69 items (Box 28)
  - Schelkinoff, S. A., 1954-1957; 2 items (Box 28)
  - Schiff, Harold I., 1978-1979; 3 items (Box 28)
  - Schindler, G. E., 1966-1967; 4 items (Box 28)
  - Schlain, Brian, 1987-1988; 4 items (Box 28)
  - Schmid, Calvin, 1986; 2 items (Box 28)
  - Schmitt, Waldo, 1947; 3 items (Box 28)
  - Schneiderman, Marvin, 1975; 1 item (Box 28)
  - Schroeder, Manfred R., 1956-1983; 7 items (Box 28)
  - Schupack, Mark, 1984; 4 items (Box 28)
  - Schurle, Arlo W., 1967; 1 item (Box 28)
  - Schwarzschild, Michael, 1977-1978; 11 item (Box 28)
  - Science and Engineering Television Journal, 1963; 5 items (Box 28)
  - Scientific File, 1970; 3 items (Box 28)
  - Sclove, Stanley, 1984; 1 item (Box 28)
  - Scott, Charles S., 1951; 1 item (Box 28)
  - Scott, Elizabeth, 1949-1954; 13 items (Box 28)
  - Scott, Gordon, 1960; 2 items (Box 28)
  - Scott, William R., 1961; 2 items (Box 28)
  - Scott, William T., 1953; 2 items (Box 28)
  - Scroggie, A. G., 1953; 1 item (Box 28)
  - Seal, K. C., 1953-1954; 4 items (Box 28)
  - Searls, Donald T., 1975-1978; 5 items (Box 28)
  - Seeger, Raymond, 1946-1948; 3 items (Box 28)
  - Segers, Richard G., 1976-1984; 6 items (Box 28)
  - Seheult, Allan, 1980-1994; 45 items (Box 28)
  - Seibert, Florence, 1949-1976; 15 items (Box 28)
  - Seidelin, Gerda, 1953; 8 items (Box 28)
    Include photo if Tukey 1953
  - Seitz, Frederick, 1983-1984; 5 items (Box 28)
  - Seiwell, H. R., 1949-1951; 32 items (Box 28)
  - Sellery, R. A., 1970; 3 items (Box 28)
  - Selvin, Hanan C., 1958; 4 items (Box 28)
  - Senko, M. E., 1966; 1 item (Box 28)
  - Serfling, Robert E., 1955; 6 items (Box 28)
  - Shafer, Glenn, 1990-1994; 7 items (Box 28)
  - Shaffer, John W., 1980; 5 items (Box 28)
  - Shannon, James, 1960; 1 item (Box 28)
  - Shapley, Harlow, 1952; 1 item (Box 28)
  - Shaw, Ralph, 1961-1962; 5 items (Box 28)
  - Shaw, Richard, 1962; 2 items (Box 28)
  - Shayer, Michael, 1990; 2 items (Box 28)
  - Shearon, Will H., 1954-1955; 8 items (Box 28)
  - Shepard, R. N., 1959; 3 items (Box 28)
  - Sheridan, Harriet, 1984; 1 item (Box 28)
  - Sherman, Bernard, 1949-1951; 25 items (Box 28)
  - Sherman, Jack, 1948; 3 items (Box 28)
  - Shewell, C. T., 1951; 7 items (Box 28)
  - Shilton, Leon, 1999; 11 items (Box 28)
  - Shindel, Larry, 1987-1988; 4 items (Box 28)
  - Shipman, J.S., 1959; 1 item (Box 28)
  - Shockley, W., 1968; 2 items (Box 28)
  - Shortley, George, 1950; 2 items (Box 28)
  - Shube, Beatrice, 1965-1986; 5 items (Box 28)
  - Shurtz, Robert, 1978-1984; 17 items (Box 28)
  - Siegel, Alberta Engvall, 1962-1978; 5 items (Box 28)
  - Siegel, Sidney, 1960-1962; 11 items (Box 28)
  - Sigler, John, 1964; 3 items (Box 28)
  - Sigma Xi, 1947-1949; 50 items (Box 28)
  - Signal Corps Engineering Laboratories, 1952-1955; 8 items (Box 28)
  - Silberstein, Irvin, 1963; 2 items (Box 28)
  - Silvey, S. D., 1974; 4 items (Box 28)
  - Simon, Herbert A., 1953-1970; 17 items (Box 28)
  - Simon, Leslie, 1946; 1 item (Box 28)
  - Simpson, Edward, 1950; 1 item (Box 28)
  - Simulmatics Corporation - Kennedy Report, 1960; 3 items (Box 28)
  - Singpurwalla, N. D., 1987; 3 items (Box 28)
  - Skelskie, Stanley, 1952; 2 items (Box 28)
  - Skin Canser Panel, 1975; 8 items (Box 28)
  - Skipper, Betty, 1990; 1 item (Box 28)
  - Slater, Paul, 1973; 2 items (Box 28)
  - Slichter, W. P., 1971-1974; 3 items (Box 28)
  - Sloan, Alfred P., 1964; 1 item (Box 28)
  - Smallwood, Hugh, 1952; 1 item (Box 28)
  - Smiley, Charles, 1948-1950; 5 items (Box 28)
  - Smillie, Wilson, 1951; 2 items (Box 29)
  - Smith, Charles Sinclair, 1977-1983; Folder 1 (Box 29)
  - Smith, Charles Sinclair, 1984-1987; Folder 2 (Box 29)
  - Smith, Craig G., 1970; 4 items (Box 29)
  - Smith, D. L., 1963; 2 items (Box 29)
  - Smith, F. B., 1953-1955; 3 items (Box 29)
  - Smith, Hugh Fairfax, 1950-1953; Folder 1 (Box 29)
  - Smith, Hugh Fairfax, 1955-1956; Folder 2 (Box 29)
  - Smith, Kennan T., 1979; 3 items (Box 29)
  - Smith, Margot W., 1968; 1 item (Box 29)
  - Smith. Jack W., 1956; 10 items (Box 29)
  - Smithies, Frank, 1938-1941; 30 items (Box 29)
  - Smyth, H. D., 1956; 1 item (Box 29)
  - Snedecor, George Waddel, 1881-, 1946-1965; 33 items (Box 29)
  - Snyder, Mitchell, 1965; 2 items (Box 29)
  - Sobel, Milton, 1919-, 1955-1958; 16 items (Box 29)
  - Society for Industrial and Applied Mathematics, 1969-1978; 9 items (Box 29)
  - Solomon, Herbert, 1949-1961; 22 items (Box 29)
  - Some Techniques for Sizing and Shaping, 3 items (Box 29)
    Includes microfiche
  - Soper, Keith, 1974-1977; 5 items (Box 29)
  - Spencer, Bruce D., 1981; 2 items (Box 29)
  - Sperry-Rand Corporation, 1955; 5 items (Box 29)
  - Spetner, L. M., 1953; 4 items (Box 29)
  - Spitzer, Frank, 1951-1964; 2 items (Box 29)
  - Spitzer, Lyman, 1946-1999; 5 items (Box 29)
  - Sponsler, George C., 1958; 2 items (Box 29)
  - Springer, Melvin D., 1952; 4 items (Box 29)
  - Sprow, Allen J., 1961-1966; 8 items (Box 29)
  - Stabb, D. J., 1977-1978; 3 items (Box 29)
  - Stahel, Werner A., 1984-1990; 10 items (Box 29)
  - Stanford Eletronics Laboratories, 1970-1971; 11 items (Box 29)
  - Stanford Linear Accelerator Center, 1973-1974; 8 items (Box 29)
  - Stanford University, 1952-1956; 9 items (Box 29)
  - Stanford University - Computer Science Advisory Committee, 1966; Folder 1 (Box 29)
  - Stanford University - Computer Science Advisory Committee, 1967-1969; Folder 2 (Box 29)
  - Stanley, J. P., 1948-1949; 2 items (Box 29)
  - Stanley, Julian C., 1967-1974; 11 items (Box 29)
  - Stanton, Frank, 1965; 2 items (Box 29)
  - Stark, Lawrence, 1959; 1 item (Box 29)